<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes"?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom">
  <channel>
    <title>Damocles on Matthew Bunge</title>
    <link>https://matthewbunge.com/tags/damocles/</link>
    <description>Recent content in Damocles on Matthew Bunge</description>
    <generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator>
    <language>en-us</language>
    <lastBuildDate>Sun, 27 Oct 2024 22:00:00 -0700</lastBuildDate><atom:link href="https://matthewbunge.com/tags/damocles/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
    <item>
      <title>Personal: I&#39;m Back (Again)</title>
      <link>https://matthewbunge.com/blog/im-back-again/</link>
      <pubDate>Sun, 27 Oct 2024 22:00:00 -0700</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://matthewbunge.com/blog/im-back-again/</guid>
      <description>Well, it&amp;rsquo;s been a while (again). I could give a long, winding story about why this site went dark for 30&amp;rsquo;ish months (again), but instead I&amp;rsquo;ll just take the opportunity to inform everyone that I&amp;rsquo;ve no longer been working at Tesla since May 2024. I loved the team I was on and it was a lot of fun.
Ok joke about the previous post on this site aside, I am legitimately currently looking for new opportunities.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Damocles: New Tools</title>
      <link>https://matthewbunge.com/blog/newtools/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 21 Dec 2020 00:05:07 -0800</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://matthewbunge.com/blog/newtools/</guid>
      <description>I just wrapped up reconfiguring Damocles to use Bootstrap and layout-wise I am extremely happy with the result. The Bootstrap integration with React is excellent and intuitive and I look forward to doing more with it. The next step is going to involve getting some more labels put up and otherwise reworking a bunch of fixed strings so it&amp;rsquo;s not like I&amp;rsquo;m going to need to wait long.
In other news, I decided to treat myself and I went and bought a number of JetBrains tools, including their web development IDE &amp;ldquo;WebStorm&amp;rdquo;.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Damocles: Casing Woes</title>
      <link>https://matthewbunge.com/blog/caseofcase/</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 11 Dec 2020 00:42:49 -0800</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://matthewbunge.com/blog/caseofcase/</guid>
      <description>I wrapped up a long running refactor of my online board game Damocles today with a deployment to Heroku. I want to focus this post on a pain point I ran into while doing this related to casing.
The purpose behind the refactor was to break up a monolithic file containing almost every React based piece of the project into separate files for all the React components. Part of this involved renaming some of the existing files, as I wanted to go from lowercase to PascalCase (ie, damoclesgame to DamoclesGame).</description>
    </item>
    
  </channel>
</rss>
