<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes"?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom">
  <channel>
    <title>Personal Site on Matthew Bunge</title>
    <link>https://matthewbunge.com/tags/personal-site/</link>
    <description>Recent content in Personal Site on Matthew Bunge</description>
    <generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator>
    <language>en-us</language>
    <lastBuildDate>Sun, 27 Oct 2024 22:00:00 -0700</lastBuildDate><atom:link href="https://matthewbunge.com/tags/personal-site/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
    <item>
      <title>Personal: I&#39;m Back (Again)</title>
      <link>https://matthewbunge.com/blog/im-back-again/</link>
      <pubDate>Sun, 27 Oct 2024 22:00:00 -0700</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://matthewbunge.com/blog/im-back-again/</guid>
      <description>Well, it&amp;rsquo;s been a while (again). I could give a long, winding story about why this site went dark for 30&amp;rsquo;ish months (again), but instead I&amp;rsquo;ll just take the opportunity to inform everyone that I&amp;rsquo;ve no longer been working at Tesla since May 2024. I loved the team I was on and it was a lot of fun.
Ok joke about the previous post on this site aside, I am legitimately currently looking for new opportunities.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Personal: I&#39;m Back</title>
      <link>https://matthewbunge.com/blog/im-back/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 09 May 2022 18:48:23 -0700</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://matthewbunge.com/blog/im-back/</guid>
      <description>Well, it&amp;rsquo;s been a while. I could give a long, winding story about why this site went dark for 18&amp;rsquo;ish months, but instead I&amp;rsquo;ll just take the opportunity to inform everyone that I&amp;rsquo;ve been working at Tesla since March 2021. I love the team I&amp;rsquo;m on and it&amp;rsquo;s been a lot of fun. There are also a lot of things they don&amp;rsquo;t want me talking about so that&amp;rsquo;s the last I&amp;rsquo;m going to say on that topic, for the time being.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Personal Site: New Site Pt. 2</title>
      <link>https://matthewbunge.com/blog/newsite2/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 07 Dec 2020 19:39:29 -0800</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://matthewbunge.com/blog/newsite2/</guid>
      <description>Today I wrapped up some outstanding issues related to the site relating to the DNS and Domain Host. In particular, I transferred the matthewbunge.com domain from GoDaddy, where I had held it for 7 years, to Namecheap. The primary motiviation was financial: the running costs of the website were reduced by approximately 55% annually. In practice, this is like 12 bucks, but saved money for no real cost is still saved money.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Personal Site: New Site</title>
      <link>https://matthewbunge.com/blog/newsite/</link>
      <pubDate>Sun, 06 Dec 2020 21:09:12 -0800</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://matthewbunge.com/blog/newsite/</guid>
      <description>My original website is years old at this point and kind of a mess, so I decided to make a new one. This time around I decided to harness the power of a static site generator. After trying a couple out, I decided to go with Hugo. I want my personal site to be more of a personal blog and I think Hugo is extremely adept at handling that use case.</description>
    </item>
    
  </channel>
</rss>
